The Pakistan Army stands for strength
courage and pride
It is a powerful symbol of the nation and an
indomitable defender of its frontiers
It is a force that has earned the respect
and admiration of the entire world
because of its bravery and tenacity in conflicts
and wars with its enemies
The Army is an ever-vigilant guardian
of the nation's security and sovereignty
It has been involved in numerous vital
operations from defending the
country's borders to providing relief to
those affected by natural disasters
Its motto of Faith Unity
Discipline is the creed of every Pakistani
soldier The Pakistan
Army speaks of India-Pakistan
relations and the enduring friendship between
the two countries It has come
a long way since its foundation and continues
to be a source of inspiration to
generations of Pakistanis